Right this way, please.
A few days ago, a man was
brought to us in a very bad condition.
Poor soul, he doesn't know who he is,
or where he's from.
Since he's been with us, he's much better.
There he is, in the front pew.
What does that have to do with us?
Well, Mr. Miller, even though
he didn't have any identification,
he did have a stack of paper with
your name and telephone number on it.
We thought that you could identify him.
Maybe he's a relative.
- What?
- Mr. Miller! Mr. Miller!
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I don't understand.
He had your name and your number.
Come on. Downtown, man. Step on it.
What happened in there?
- Who was that old guy?
- Craziness.
Who knows? Some fucking degenerate,
bum, wino. I don't know.
What did he do to you
to make you act so crazy?
What did he do? Fucking guy
gripped my hand. Touched my hand.
You didn't recognize him at all?
- Why should I recognize him, man?
- The nun said it could be a relative.
Yeah. For real.
You never knew your father.
Carol, please, darlin',
what are you saying?
Nothing, please.
Don't even say something like that.
This guy's some degenerate,
some bum, some wino, some nobody.
That's all. I don't know what the hell
we were doing down there in the first place.
Then why did he have
your name and phone number
on a piece of paper in his pocket?
He probably found it in the garbage
while he was looking for his lunch.
We're here now.
Keep that meter rolling, all right?
Just keep that meter rolling.
- We're here now.
- Hurry up.
She'll be just a second, all right, pal.
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
I'm trying to put the hole here.
You're gonna kill yourself.
Give me this thing, man.
- Okay.
- Wait.
Give me this. Watch, watch, watch.
Okay, get back, get back.
What do you want over here?
- I want it right there.
- Where?
- You want to put a hole right here?
- Yeah.
- All right. Right there? Okay.
No!
- I think I want it over there.
- Over here?
- On the right side.
- On this side?
All right.
No! No! I want it over there.
- Over here?
- Mm-hm.
- Okay. Right there?
No!
- What do you want?
- I think I want it up there.
You want it up there?
- Over here?
- To the center.
All right, all right,
all right, all right. You're sure?
- Uh-huh.
- All right.
Look at this.
"Ernesto Williams,
a 50-year-old truck driver
"broke down and wept
as he talked about his son Lewis,
"who is accused of hijacking a bus
and killing two people.
"All his life he's been depressed,
always been down.
"He's a very emotional boy."
I like the .44 killer better.
Oh, God. Listen to this.
"Mrs. Patricia Adams of Queens village
gave her poodle a bath,
"and being late
for a beauty parlor appointment,
"placed the dog
in a microwave oven to dry it off.
"When she turned the oven on,
the poodle exploded.
"The woman died of a heart attack."
Con. Perfect name for him.
Holy Christ, man! What is this?
They send us the bill
for Madison Square Garden?
What? Are they kidding me, man?
How the hell are we supposed
to pay this bill? Is it for three months?
That's the bill for one month.
Christ! What have we got here?
A refrigerator, a couple of lights?
The tele... Oh, man. Telephone.
- Oh, no! Houston, Texas.
- My mother.
L.A., look at this:
L.A., $1.50, L.A., $2.75.
- L.A., $7.50, man.
- Yeah, they're mine.
You talk to L.A.
for two hours and ten minutes, man?
What, are you going out of your mind?
What, are you crazy? Holy Christ!
- Philadelphia?
- My sister.
- Miami.
- That's mine.
Trenton, New Jersey. Queens.
Man... Wait, Queens is a local call.
"Payment of the full amount
for telephone service
"is required by this date to avoid
interruption of your outgoing service,
"and five days later
termination of your incoming service."
That's tomorrow. They're gonna
come and turn it off tomorrow.
Turn it off, huh?
We sell this Buffalo,
everything is gonna change.
We're gonna have enough money
to do what we want when we want to.
We'll be able to get everything we need.
First thing I'm gonna get
is snakeskin boots.
Oh, yeah, man,
we're gonna get lots of clothes.
And get a boat.
Buy ourselves some motorcycles.
And we'll go away. Go to Jamaica.
Morocco. Go to Nepal.
Wherever we are, man,
we're gonna go out every night.
You're never gonna know
how much I will pay you.
'You never knew your father.
'Who was that guy?'
It's not only hate.
It's all around you, this city.
'You said you never knew your father.'
Now you're gonna see it.
What's gonna happen?
Oh, God.
Reno!
Sorry, I'm late.
- Listen, I have something for you.
- Yeah? What have you got?
Come on. Take it.
Bye.
Hello?
Antonio.
Well, how are you, darling?
Where've you been, you little devil?
I've missed you.
Oh, I see.
What is it, Bruce?
Well, what you do
is you call Lloyds of London,
and you have them insure it for $300,000.
Do you think you can do that?
Well, good.
I'm sorry.
Listen, I picked you up a little trinket.
No, no, I'm not gonna tell you what it is.
I'll show it to you.
Later.
Tonight?
Excuse me.
What is it, Bruce?
Oh. Okay, show him right in.
Antonio... I'll see you later, okay?
Ciao.
- Reno, Reno, it's good to see you.
- Good to see you, Dalton.
- Please, sit down.
- Thank you very much.
So... tell me, when am I gonna see it?
- Just as soon as I finish with it.
- As soon as it's finished?
You mean the masterpiece
isn't finished yet, Mr. Miller?
Almost. I need another week.
I need a favor from you first, though.
I'm gonna need an extra 500.
$500 now, and two months ago it was
$200 for your girlfriend's abortion.
And three weeks later,
it was $150 for extra material costs.
This'll be the final favor. I just need
that 500 to keep the landlord off my back.
For Christ's sake. If it isn't one thing
with you, it's another, isn't it, Mr. Miller?
Oh, come on, Dalton. It's only $500.
This is gonna be my greatest piece.
Wait till you see it. You'll love it.
Give me that 500, and I'll give you
that painting in one week.
No.
And that's final?
That's final, Mr. Miller.
Reno!
Whoa! Carol!
How did it go today?
Okay, I'll see you later, baby.
Okay, Al, here's the rent for one month.
That's very good, you know,
but you're still one month behind.
And come Monday, two months behind.
What are you gonna do about that?
Don't worry about it.
Reno's almost finished with the Buffalo
and as soon as he's done, we'll be able
to pay you all the rent that we owe you.
You don't pay up, everything's
gonna be out on the street.
Oh, it's not me.
You know, I just work for him.
It's the people in the building
I worry about.
Hey, they're gonna call the marshal.
They'll take all your pretty stuff,
and put it out on the street.
You're gonna have to sit out there
and watch it. People are gonna take it.
Everybody's gonna know
you didn't pay the rent.
Don't worry. Like I said,
the painting's almost finished.
Worry?
I ain't the one that's got to worry.
You gotta worry.
Where the hell is this?
See, they're really good friends of mine,
and they need a place
to rehearse for only one month.
- This place is filthy.
- Oh, I'll clean it. I love to clean.
- No, you don't want this place.
- It's beautiful!
It'll cost you a lot of money.
How much?
We'll take it. It's great! Beautiful!
500 a month. Cash.
Has it got a toilet?
You won't make much noise, will you?
Violins. We're a violin group.
Can anyone tell him? We're a violin group.
- The money.
- Give him the money.
It's finished.
And you know we need the money,
so why don't you face up to it?
Oh, so it's finished? Thank you.
It's finished. Since when did you
become such an expert on painting?
You're telling me it's finished? What
do you know about painting anyway?
Really? What do you know about painting?
I'll tell you what you know about
painting, man. You don't know nothing.
You know what you know about?
You know about how to bitch,
and how to eat, and how to bitch,
and how to shit, and how to bitch,
but you don't know nothing about painting,
so I'll tell you when it's gonna be done.
And about the money, man.
I don't wanna hear about that money.
It's all you talk about,
it's all the other one talks about,
that's all I hear
from that fag art dealer uptown,
and I don't wanna hear it, 'cause
the sound of that word drives me crazy!
You know what I think about money?
I'll tell you what I think about money.
See this? This is what I think
about money. This, all right?
It's a gag now. You ready?
Throw it up in my face.
You've been wanting to say it. Say it!
Say how you've been paying the bills.
How you've been spending your money.
How you picked up the rent last month.
What do you want me to do?
Get on my knees? Kiss your feet?
Well, forget it, man, because this place
has been here long before you got here,
and it's gonna be here
long after you leave, all right?
So, don't tell me about money, about
painting or when this thing is finished.
I'll tell you when
it's gonna get finished.
In fact, you'll be the first to know.
I'll come and tell you, man.
I'll come up to you wherever you are.
Even if you're sleeping, man.
I'll sneak up to you, man.
I'll whisper it in your ear, man.
I'll say, "It's done!"
'Please, let me out.'
Oh, come on.
I don't wanna spend another night
just sitting around looking at the TV.
We have to. We have no money.
But I thought you got
your al... ala... alo... al...
- Alimony.
- Al-i-mony check today.
I did, but I had to pay the rent with it.
Never!
We don't have any... drugs.
We don't have any money.
We don't have any dope.
I can't take it anymore!
Well, why don't you call up
one of your friends and go out?
Because I don't have any friends.
Listen, baby, I wanna say
something about last night.
I don't know what got into me.
But I didn't mean one word of that.
Yes, you did. You mean every word of it.
Ah, come on, now.
Come on. You know I couldn't say
those things to you and mean it.
You know I wouldn't talk that way to you.
It's just lately...
You know how I am when I'm painting.
Yeah, you were never like that before.
Yeah, but things were different before.
Got so much more at stake now, man.
We got so much riding on this thing here.
Oh, good. That's the band. I've gotta go.
Boys, come on, boys. Come on,
a little louder, a little louder. Perfect.
Hey, why don't you call
your friends down here?
There's others people living
in the building besides them.
Why don't you cool it?
# 'Cause I'm a fool for you
# 'Cause I'm a fool for you... #
Who are these clowns, anyway?
They're called The Roosters.
Pam knows the lead singer.
Tony Coca-Cola from the club.
They rented out the sixth floor
to rehearse.
Tony Coca-Cola. The Roosters.
What is that, some kind of fucking joke?
How did they find out about this place?
- Pam told them about it.
- Tsk. Figures.
They're not gonna be here long.
They really sound good on their album.
An album? These guys have an album?
What, are you kidding?
I'd quit painting in protest.
Listen, I'm going out where I can get
some peace of mind.
Change the station.
Yeah. There.
Uh-uh.
No.
- Come on, make up your mind.
- No, no.
- This is where we started from.
- Okay.
'Now, introducing an amazing
new electrical device: Porto-Pak.
'Use with any household appliance,
wherever electricity is not available.
'At the beach, camping,
or just around the house.
'Lightweight, easy to use
with any electrical appliance.
'Hairdryer, electric shaver,
blenders, toasters, vacuum cleaners,
'stereo, power tools, even radio and TV.
'Anything that plugs into your wall
sockets will plug into Porto-Pak.
'That's right, Porto-Pak. Only $19.95.
Discover Porto-Pak now.
'Available at Macy's, Gimbels, Two Guys,
'and any participating
hardware store near you.
'Get it now.
Porto-Pak. That's just $19.95.
'Porto-Pak.'
Ritchy... Ritchy.
Let's hear you play.
# Mickey was a poor boy
# His mama swept the beauty parlor
# He came from a side of town
# Where the little girls swore
they would not swallow
# No!
# Oop!
# Oop-cha-do-a! #
Come on, these are nice girls.
They're trying to do this, you know...
They want... All right, Ritchy, let's go.
Brown...
Yellow...
It's two in the morning, guys.
# Mickey was a poor boy
# His mama swept the beauty parlor
# And he came from a side of town
# Where the little girls swore
That they would not swallow... #
Oh! Hold on! Slow down a minute!
Let's take it from the top,
but it's gotta be punchy.
The 'oop' is a punch.
# Oop-cha-do-ba #
You know where to come in.
Just punch it in.
You're holding back. You're not coming in
on the first time. The song's cooking.
No, you're not coming in on the first.
The second time... boom!
A-cha-do-ba! Ritchy...
# Mickey was a poor boy
His mama swept... #
Is that a chorus I'm hearing?
More voices.
Oh, dear God!
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing here, huh?
How come you're sleeping here?
How come you're not home
with your old lady?
How come you're on the street,
not with the people that love you, man?
Where do you come from?
Come on, talk to me.
I'm here waiting for you, baby.
You got a sad, sad story, man?
What happened?
Your girlfriend left you?
No, you went and fucked the shit
out of your landlord, huh?
Come on, man! Wake up!
I'm rapping here, baby! Wake up!
- I need a dime.
- I ain't got no dime. Stand up, man.
Get up, man. You don't need no dime.
Come on, stand up, stand up, stand up.
You don't need no dime.
Shit.
Oh, fuck, man.
# She was still in high school
Tony, I wanna talk to you about the girls
you brought in here for background singing.
I don't think they look good.
They don't look good with you,
or with anybody else in the band.
And it's not just me who thinks that,
the other girls think so, too. They don't fit in.
One sits there and snaps her gum,
opens her blue eyes,
the other one sits there cracking.
They don't even do anything right.
They don't fit in with the whole thing.
I just don't like them there.
I don't know what they're doing.
"Oop-cha-doop." They don't even know
the words to the song.
They sit there, you show 'em 12 times.
You gotta go back over it.
You know, they're just... It's incredible
what you'll come up with to put in a band.
I don't think you need it.
Tony, I don't think you need them
in the band at all.
Tony, are you listening to me?
'Dear Carol,
'I came across this picture of us,
which reminded me
'this Thursday is the fifth anniversary
of the first time we met.
'I just thought I'd send you
this little something extra.
'I want you to know
that I think of you often.
'Love, always, Steven.'
Listen, I can't even think
with these guys playing.
It's all day and all night.
They don't quit for a minute.
These guys don't even stop
to go to the bathroom.
It's not my problem. It's your problem.
What do you mean, it's my problem?
It's your job to keep this place quiet.
My job? It's not my job.
Besides, they don't bother me.
But why should they bother you?
What are you doing sitting fixing plugs?
Night time comes, you drink
your few beers, man. Watch TV.
Me, I gotta work.
With them guys playing, I can't work.
Look, I can work,
and they don't bother me.
I ain't fooling around, man.
Look, you need to get rid of them cats,
or I ain't paying the rent.
What do you mean, you're not paying
the rent? You don't pay the rent anyway.
- Hey, don't worry.
- I can't work with these guys.
I'll tell 'em to lay it down. I'll tell 'em
the police are complaining.
- I got it.
- All right, do something.
- Come here, come here, come here.
- What have you got?
It's a present for you
and your girlfriend.
It's a rabbit.
Hey, you know how to cook it?
It's delicious.
Better than chicken.
'Reno.'
- 'Reno!'
- Carol?
'Reno.'
Carol?
'Reno!'
Carol.
Carol?
Carol, come here.
'Reno? Reno!'
- Carol?
- 'Reno, Reno. Reno.
'Reno, Reno, Reno. Reno.'
Carol.
- 'Reno. Reno!'
- Carol?
'Reno! Reno!'
'Reno! Reno! Reno...'
Hey, look at me.
Come on. Look at me.
I'm surprised you didn't wake up for me.
Come on.
Listen to me. Come on. Come on, man.
Wake up. Come on, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
Wake up, man. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, open up your eyes.
You're all fucked up.
Oh, my God!
...Roosters!
Let's take it from...
- Are we gonna go to this club or what?
- In a minute.
"In a minute."
That's what you told me half hour ago.
Come on, this is the first time
we're all going out together in months.
Yeah, look who we have to go with.
Well, they were nice enough
to give us the tickets.
Besides, they're a dynamite band.
You'll dig 'em once you hear 'em.
Once I hear 'em?
I hear that show day and night.
It's nothing like hearing 'em in a club.
Yeah, at least in a club,
you can walk out.
Stop complaining.
We're gonna have a good time.
- You almost ready?
- Mm-hm.
Hey, toro...
Hey, toro!
Tony's so great, the way he
dresses up in women's clothes.
He has better things than what we have.
Like silky nightgowns,
leather garter belts.
He makes himself up so beautifully.
I mean, you just don't meet people
like that anymore. Anywhere.
Nope.
Hey!
Hey, toro.
Who you looking at?
I'll cut your eye out, man!
Oh...
I wouldn't hurt you.
I wouldn't hurt you, man.
Uh-uh. Not you. Never. Love you.
Love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you.
Not you. I love you.
Hey, toro!
One, two, three, four!
All right! Thank you! Whoo!
So, what's this Reno dude
that you two live with?
Uh, he's an artist, he's a painter.
Yeah? What, do you all fuck him?
Who fucks who? Who fucks what?
- It's none of your fucking business.
- "It's none of your fucking business"?
Well, I'll tell you something
that is my business, and that's Tony.
I don't like you. I don't mind you
hanging out listening to the music.
That don't bother me. But when you start
getting too close to Tony, I get pissed.
He's my property, and when you start
fucking with my property, I get pissed.
- You have a property badge?
- Yes, I do have a property badge.
And if I see you fucking with Tony
too much, I'm gonna fuck with you.
Okay, well, you do what you wanna do,
I'll do what I wanna do. And...
- Excuse me.
- Well, just watch what you wanna do.
Fucking bitch.
Get it, get it, yeah.
So, how much is Briggs
gonna give us for the Buffalo?
Ah, you bastard.
Depends on how much he likes it.
You mean it depends
on how much he likes you.
Well, yeah, probably.
You should let him
stick it up your ass once.
Use KY Jelly. It won't hurt.
I think that color's good.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna send you a bill for this.
- A little bit more.
- Shut up.
Two minutes till showtime!
My shirt!
Don't you call me a fucking coke...
Fuck you! Give me that.
- Here. Come here.
- Your bag.
- I don't want that.
- I need somebody's pussy!
I wanna see somebody's pussy!
I want you downstairs...
Let's go.
Get the drum pad.
Everybody, out!
Move, girls!
Out!
Come on!
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
you fucking want this!
Elvis Presley, eat your heart out now,
'cause we got Tony Coca-Cola!
Playing a little rock'n'roll
with his band, The Roosters.
Hey, Tony, you gonna step now?
You're gonna step?
Come on, you guys, step.
Tony Coca-Cola's gonna sing!
How come you're not up front
with everybody else?
'Cause the music's too loud.
What do you mean, the music's too loud?
You like your music loud.
You play all your records loud.
You used to like bars, too.
Don't you remember how we were?
We used to sit in the corner,
and we used to get really drunk.
We used to walk home laughing and singing.
Reno, look at me.
Where are you now, baby?
What's happening to you?
Hey, old buddy!
What are you doing out here tonight?
Night traveler, I see, huh?
Did you stop by to have a drink with me?
Hey, what you got in your hand, mister?
A drill! Hey, what are you, a fix-it man?
What have you got, bankers' hours?
It looks like you're working 12 to 12.
I wouldn't want that kind of job.
I tell you what,
there's no job in the world
that I know is worth getting out of bed
in the morning for.
And I know something else that's good
for jobs that give you a pain in the neck.
This good old warm bottle right here.
Have a drink, buddy...
Come on, mister. Cool it, now.
Come on, don't get excited.
What have you got, problems or something?
What have you got?
Problems with your old lady?
Ah! I thought so, huh?
She's taking you across the...
Giving you a hard time.
Well, I'll tell you something,
I've got the same problem myself, man.
And I got one word of advice for you:
I would...
What?
What? New York?
Hi.
Dad...
I'm getting married, Dad.
Dad! I want your blessing, Dad.
I want your blessing!
Hm, where's my dad?
Daddy!
Goddamn!
Pop!
Bus! Wait, driver.
Driver, take good care of my father.
Excuse me, sir, you're blocking
my entrance to the subway.
So I says to him, "Excuse me,
but I gotta sleep, know what I mean?"
So, so...
Robbie!
What the hell...
Take it easy, take it easy.
I'm nothing to you!
I saw nothing, I swear to God!
Go on! What the fuck is wrong with you?
Go on!
Mm.
That's good.
Any onions... No onions...
Yeah, come in. It's open.
Is Pamela here, man?
Pamela? No, Pamela's not here now.
Wow, a buffalo, man.
Sensational.
I brought Pamela a present, man.
What's up, dawg?
Electric lips.
Little dog.
This is a whacked-up thing, man.
Do you ever get
into a rock'n'roll trip, baby?
Posters?
Portraits?
I mean...
How do you do this, man?
How is this done, brother?
How's what done?
I mean... if somebody
needed something special,
a thing, could you do it?
What are you talking about, man?
I need something special.
Like this. But me.
Could you do that?
You wanna know if I could do a painting
of you? If I could do your portrait?
Yeah, I could do your portrait.
It'll cost you 500.
420.
Okay, okay, five, five.
But I need it right away.
I need it now. When can we start?
Listen, can you believe this?
"Man found dead last night
in hallway of 895 Bowery.
"Although he was found
to have no money or identification,
"the police suspect that
robbery was not the motive.
"The man appeared to be a member
of the destitute population of that area.
"Police autopsy revealed the man was
murdered by some type of power tool,
"possibly an electric drill."
What are you trying to do to me?
- What are you trying to do to me?
- What are you talking about?
What are you trying to do to me?
- You're trying to drive me crazy, huh.
- Why are you looking at me like that?
You're driving me nuts.
Why are you doing this to me? Why?
Why are you doing this to me, man?
Why are you making me like this? Why?
I got pizza for everybody.
Careful. It's really hot.
So, while I'm in the parlor,
this creepy old guy comes up to me,
and says, "Sweetie, you don't have
to kiss to make babies."
So, I waited
until it was about time to leave,
and I walked up to him and I said,
"No, but you gotta fuck."
Mm.
Oh, so guess what? Good news.
I've got us free tickets for us
to go see Iggy Pop at the Palladium
with Dee Dee... Ramone.
Pammy, you wanna bite
with some peppers on?
No.
Ask her. Maybe she wants a bite.
I hate him, I hate him, I hate him!
'Hello? Hello?'
Hello, Steven? This is Carol.
Mr. Reno.
It's a very simple philosophy, Mr. Reno.
It's very, very simple.
That's the kind of idea
I think we should, huh...
But, man, look, what is it?
What...? The colors?
You must know? You must feel a color.
You must feel me.
What is it of me that
you're putting on here?
You don't talk to me.
You're trying to scare me, man.
Don't talk, babe!
You aren't communicating!
Bitch... Son of a bitch.
"The 27th spirit is Ronové."
"He appeareth in the form of a monster.
"He teaches the art of rhetoric very well,
and giveth good servants...
"...knowledge of tongues,
favors with friends or foes.
"He's a marquis and a great earl,
"and under his command,
19 legions of spirits."
# Ronové.
# I'm calling you, Ronové! #
Shut the fuck up!
Son of a bitch!
It's finished. Done, baby...
It's all done. I just finished.
Just finished it, sweet.
I just finished it.
No, no, no, no.
This isn't right.
This is nothing. This is shit!
Where's the impact?
It's just a goddamn buffalo!
This is nothing like your other works.
This is far from your best stuff,
and the size can't hide it!
Reno, the worst thing that can happen
to a painter is happening to you.
You're becoming simply a technician.
There's nothing there.
There's no feeling,
there's no drama, there's no passion.
This is totally unacceptable!
It's a waste of my time.
I can do nothing with this.
I'd be ashamed to show this to anyone!
It's a mockery.
It's a work of pure unadulterated ego!
It is absolutely worthless!
Worthless, worthless,
worthless, worthless, worthless!
I can't stand this a moment longer.
Who would've thought
it would come to this? Worthless!
How dare you, you fucking bastard?
You fucker! We're not staying with you!
Do something!
# Nobody's my girlfriend
# Nobody's my friend
# All my love is gone
# No one in the world
# I've got a broken heart
# Don't let me get started
# And I ain't got a girlfriend
# Oh, no, no
# I ain't got no girlfriend
# Nobody's my girl
# Nobody takes me around
# Nobody holds me
# Nobody's my friend
# Oh, no, no... #
Carol...
Carol!
Carol? Carol? Carol!
Carol.
Carol! Carol!
Carol!
Carol! Wait a minute!
- Carol, wait here a minute!
- Don't you touch me!
- Where are you going?
- I'm leaving!
- You ain't leaving.
- I don't need it.
I don't believe you.
One thing goes wrong,
and you leave us, man.
I don't need you, bitch.
Your stuff, man!
Stuff!
Shit, man.
You're gonna need your stuff, baby.
Baby?
Come back for your stuff, man!
You need your suitcase.
You need your suitcase, man!
Carol? Carol, yeah, it's me.
Carol. Hello, baby. How you doing?
Fine, fine, fine.
She will be.
We'll... we'll be there.
Later on? Sure.
'Yes, hello? This is Briggs speaking.'
This is Reno.
'Yes, Reno. What is it?'
Dalton... I have to speak to you tonight.
There's something very important
I have to show you.
'What, another buffalo?'
No, not a buffalo.
Something different.
Something you're going to like very much.
'Can't we talk about it
up at the gallery tomorrow?'
No, this can't wait until tomorrow.
I have to speak to you about it tonight.
You have to come down here tonight.
'Down there? Now?
It's the middle of the night.'
This is important.
I have to make it up to you
for what I showed you today.
It's something
you're gonna like very much.
I sent the girls away,
so we could look at it... alone.
'Alone? You're all alone, Reno?'
Yes. I'll be alone.
All night.
Just waiting for you.
'Listen...
'I'll be down, but give me some time
to get ready.
'Is 45 minutes all right?'
Sure.
'Maybe I'll bring down
a bottle of wine with me.
'Wine and bread...'
Bread?
Bring bread.
'45 minutes then.'
Goodbye, Dalton.
Reno? Reno?
Reno?
Are you here?
Reno? Where are you?
What...? Who's there?
Who is that?
Reno?
Reno...
Reno.
Now what is this?
What do you think you're doing?
Reno, put that thing down!
Reno.
Listen to me, Reno. Don't be a fool!
This afternoon I was wrong
about the buffalo, all right?
Reno, please, listen to me.
Please, listen to me, Reno!
Reno, please! My God!
Reno, no!
What are you doing?
Come here, come here, come here.
Come here.
Come here. Pammy, come here.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
I'm gonna go take a shower, now.
Okay. I'll bring the tea to the bedroom.
Steven, you're not asleep yet, are you?
Oh, you've kept the bed so warm.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
Steven... come closer.
Steven...
- Are you avoiding me now?
- Uh-huh.
Steven, come here.
Steven...
Oh, Steven...
Steven.
Come here.
'...telling me that I'm not
a respectable person in this world.
'Excuse me! Am I a respectable person?
That's right!
'Right over here. You got...
You got a quarter?
'I take the... God bless you.
God bless you.
'Ah, son of a...'